<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>AntiCrash - less crashes!</name>
    <directory>anticrash</directory>
    <id>2784448102</id>
    <description>Have you ever had a [i]truly[/i] broken build where you were afraid to attack anything because the game would crash or freeze? This mod solves this issue, letting you enjoy the game without the anxiety of that ruining your run.

After your game crashes once, AntiCrash will begin protecting your run by preventing certain visual effects from occurring and limiting the amount of lasers on-screen. Due to how this game works, doing so results in a much more stable experience while still maintaining a good level of performance. AntiCrash also checks for item builds that are known to always crash the game due to various bugs and warns you if you have one, as well as making the Tear Detonator safer to use.

You can always see if AntiCrash is enabled for the current run via a presence of a purple dot in the bottom left of the screen, and a red dot while it's actively working.

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2681875787]Mod Config Menu[/url] support is included, so you can toggle the mod and adjust settings with ease.

Disclaimer: AntiCrash does not eliminate all possible crashes from the game, and it will sacrifice some performance for stability while active.

If you've encountered a crash with this mod installed and would like for me to look into it, please check this Discussion thread for info on how to report it: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2784448102/3265680184989696685/]Bug reports[/url].

[hr][/hr]
If you've enjoyed this mod, check out my other mods [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2784126187]in this list[/url]! Also, consider leaving a like so that others can also find and enjoy this mod.</description>
    <version>1.16</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
</metadata>
